<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mental Health Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="cbtdesc">Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT) is a method of therapy that focuses on challenging and changing unhelpful cognitive distortions (e.g. thoughts, beliefs, and attitudes) and behaviors that might affect someone. By recognizing the distorted thoughts and developing healthy coping mechanisms that target solving current problems, one will begin to experience relief from symptoms. Originally, it was designed to treat depression, but its use has been expanded to include treatment of a number of mental health conditions, including anxiety.</string>
    <string name="list_of_cognitive_distortions">List of Cognitive Distortions</string>
    <string name="allcogdist"><b>All-or-nothing thinking:</b> You see your situation as black and white, you want to have everything or nothing. Everything is unreachable perfection, and consequently you feel like you have nothing. But that’s far from the truth.\n\n<b>Overgeneralization:</b> You generalize one bad event that happened to you (rejection, for example) as a never-ending pattern that you can’t do anything about.\n\n<b>Mental filter:</b> You see only negatives and minuses and ignore all the benefits and pluses.\n\n<b>Discounting the positives:</b> You give zero value to your past accomplishments, strengths and positive qualities. They don’t count, because everyone has them.\n\n<b>Jumping to conclusions, Mind reading, and Catastrophizing:</b> You predict that things will turn out badly, even if you don’t have any proof for that, or you assume people will react negatively or reject you, again without any proof. Catastrophizing is jumping to negative conclusions on steroids.\n\n<b>Magnification or minimization:</b> You make a big deal out of small, not really important details, or you shrink things that are important to almost nothing.\n\n<b>Emotional reasoning:</b> You draw the conclusion that how you temporarily feel is who you really are. For example: “I feel like I didn\’t write this well enough, so I must really be a bad writer”.\n\n<b>“Should statements”:</b> You criticize yourself and others based on what you or they should, must, or have to do. You moralize to others and yourself.\n\n<b>Labeling:</b> You put a negative label on your identity based on perceived shortcomings, even if they’re not real. “I’m a complete loser”, would be a nice example.\n\n<b>Blame and personalization:</b> You blame yourself for things that were not your responsibility or you blame others for things that were your responsibility. Or you assume that no matter what other people do, they do it to block you or harm you personally. You also constantly compare yourself to others.\n\n<b>Always be right:</b> Being wrong is simply unthinkable to you. You try to prove that every one of your actions or thoughts is correct. You try to persuade others to think the same way you do.\n\n<b>Fallacy of fairness:</b> You feel resentful or envious, because you think you know better what would be a fairer situation, than other people do.\n\n<b>Fallacy of change:</b> You expect other people to change or the world to change more to your liking and wants. And your happiness seems to depend on that kind of change.\n\n<b>Fallacy of being a good person:</b> You expect being a good person and sacrificing for others will pay off somehow and when it doesn\’t you feel bitter.\n\n<b>Hindsight thinking and what-ifs:</b> You look back at your past decisions and make judgments how you could handle things better. But you handled it according to your knowledge and experience at that time. In the same way, you might constantly ask yourself “what if” about your future, but you’re never satisfied with the answer.\n\n<b>Control error:</b> You either see yourself as a helpless being with no personal power or control. Consequently, you feel stuck and externally controlled. The other extreme is if you feel responsible for everything and want to control everything.\n\n<b>Unrealistic comparison:</b> You compare yourself with other people, viewing them better as you are, not considering different starting points, life circumstances, genetic advantages, random luck events etc.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_anti_procrastination">AntiProcrastination</string>
    <string name="antiproc">
        1) <b>Create a Daily Activity Schedule</b> (for when feeling disorganized and nothing to do, plan out every hour of day)\n \n
        2) <b>Antiprocrastination Sheet</b> (if tasks feel unrewarding, write down why they seem so and put predictions to test when doing said tasks)\n \n
        3) <b>Daily Record of Dysfunctional Thoughts</b> (if paralyzed by urge to do nothing, write down why feel urge to do nothing and realize motivation follows action, not vice versa)\n \n
        4) <b>Pleasure-Predicting Sheet</b> (when not feeling like doing things alone, predict enjoyment from doing activity beforehand, then do it and see how you feel after doing it. See how being alone/with others impacts it)\n \n
        5) <b>But-Rebuttal</b> (when giving excuses, combat the buts with logical and realistic rebuttals until you can feel comfortable actually doing the task)\n \n
        6) <b>Self-Endorsement</b> (when feeling like what you do isn\'t worth much, write down self-downing thoughts and find distorted patterns in them, while listing accomplishments each day completed)\n \n
        7) <b>TIC-TOC Technique</b> (when task is thought about in self-defeating manner, think about things in task oriented way rather than task interfering way)\n
        </string>
    <string name="antiproc2">
        8) <b>Breaking Tasks Down into Small, Actionable Steps</b> (for when feeling overwhelmed by everything that has to be done)\n \n
        9) <b>Motivation Without Coercion</b> (feeling guilty and duty bound, eliminate shoulds when giving self instructions, and try to find joy in task in terms of what you want to do, rather than what you must do)\n \n
        10) <b>Disarming Technique</b> (feeling like being pressured into something and resentful, assertively agree and tell them you are capable of doing it on your own)\n \n
        11) <b>Visualize Success</b> (when having difficulty modifying habit imagine self with positive benefits of changing habit after relaxing)\n \n
        12) <b>Count What Counts</b> (when feeling incapable of doing stuff on own, count number of times can do things on own, and reduce dwelling on inadequacies)\n \n
        13) <b>Test Can\'ts</b> (when feeling incapable, set up experiment and tackle the can\'ts which will prove negative predictions)\n \n
        14) <b>Can\'t Lose</b> (when fearing failure, write down any negative consequences of failure and adopt coping strategy ahead of time)\n
    </string>
    <string name="whymethod">Continually ask follow up question of <i>why?</i> when you notice a problem going on. Eventually after enough whys the root of the problem will be found and then the solution to the problem can be formulated accordingly.\n\n1. Write down very specifically what your problem is\n\n2. List everyone affected and how they’re related to your problem (supporters, blockers …)\n\n3. Gather all the data that explain and support the problem – data, facts etc.\n\n4. Start asking yourself <i>why</i> at least five times or more and find one or more root causes\n\n5. Find a proportionate solution for every step of the process\n\n6. Prepare a plan for getting rid of the root cause\n\n7. Communicate constructively with other affected people how you will eliminate the root cause</string>
    <string name="schemaoverview">Schema therapy is an integrative psychotherapy combining theory and techniques from previously existing therapies, including cognitive behavioral therapy, psychoanalytic object relations theory, attachment theory, and Gestalt therapy. The goal is to identify maladaptive schemas (ie, thought patterns) in childhood that led to unhealthy coping mechanisms as an adult, and to overwrite them to meet one\'s emotional needs that are likely being neglected.</string>
    <string name="discrej">Disconnection and Rejection</string>
</resources>
