<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:layout_marginRight="4dp"
    tools:context=".Guilt">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="655dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="4dp">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView3"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                android:text="First Aid for Guilt"
                android:textAllCaps="true"
                android:textSize="24dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView4"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginStart="4dp"
                android:layout_marginLeft="4dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="250dp"
                android:text="1) Learn Recipe for Effective Apology \n\nA proper apology includes the following things:\n\na) A statement of regret for what happened; \nb) a clear “I’m sorry” statement; \nc) a request for forgiveness—all of which must be delivered with sincerity; \nd) validating the other person’s feelings, which is done by showcasing accuracy in conveying understanding of what happened back to the person, recognizing how they felt, acknowledging their feelings are reasonable, and conveying empathy and remorse for their emotional state; \ne) offering atonement or financial compensation if applicable; \nf) acknowledging we violated expectations to help assure it won't happen again \n\n2) Forgive Yourself For Mistakes\n\nIf you're not able to receive forgiveness from the person you wronged, don't let the guilt poison your every day life. Must recognize we've beaten ourselves up enough and that excessive guilt serves no productive purpose going forward. The steps to attain self-forgiveness are as follows:\n\nAcknowledging the severity of the incident, the wrongdoings, and the impact on the person harmed both practically and emotionally. This process can be uncomfortable, if not outright painful to go through, but granting the self-forgiveness can free us in the long run. Some exercises for self-forgiveness include:\n\nAccountability - Describe the actions/inactions that led to the other person feeling harmed. Go through that description and take out any qualifiers/excuses from the explanation. Summarize the harm the other person sustained both emotionally and tangibly. Go through the description of harm and amkes sure it is as realistic and accurate as possible. Then, consider the circumstances of the situation. Did you intend for the events to happen, and if not, what extenuating circumstances got in the way? The idea is not to excuse your actions but to understand where they came from so that you can forgive yourself.\n\nAtonement - Take action to minimize the likelihood of the incident occurring again. After that, identify significant tasks, contributions, or commitments that would make forgiveness feel well-earned. Make a clear mark of when you've earned your self-forgiveness so that you can literally close the book on your guilt for good. \n\n3) Reengage in Life\n\nWhen dealing with Survivor's Guilt, focus on the people and obligations remaining and empower yourself to get through that way.\n\nWhen dealing with Separation Guilt, write a paragraph describing how you are handling a relational dynamic and focus on how self-care and proper boundaries can make you a better person overall.\n\nIf dealing with Disloyalty Guilt, write about how you have the right to live your life as you wish and don't need to uphold other's expectations in the process."
                android:textSize="20dp"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</android.support.constraint.ConstraintLayout>